{
    "id": "3427f2ee2931480d89830ba5f9503660",
    "title": "Exclamations Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How charming ……………………….!",
            "description": "In exclamations the subject goes before the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "she is",
                "she does"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. lovely morning it is!",
            "description": "Use what a before adjective + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "What a",
                "How",
                "How a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… tall she has grown!",
            "description": "Use how before an adjective without noun.",
            "answers": [
                "What a",
                "How",
                "How a"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… beautiful house you have!",
            "description": "Use what a before adjective + noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "What a",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… quickly the holidays passed!",
            "description": "Use how before adjective or adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "What a",
                "What",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. fool he is!",
            "description": "Use what a before a noun or noun + adjective. Use how before an adjective or adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How a",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. tragedy!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How a",
                "What a",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. brilliant idea it was!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… clever girl she is!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… well she dances!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "What",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… sweet the mangoes are!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "What a",
                "How a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… beautifully she sings!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How a",
                "What a"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}